<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>updates on Practical Go - Book Website</title>
    <link>https://practicalgobook.net/categories/updates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in updates on Practical Go - Book Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://practicalgobook.net/categories/updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The server powering practicalgobook.net</title>
      <link>https://practicalgobook.net/posts/blog_internals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://practicalgobook.net/posts/blog_internals/</guid>
      <description>I write my blog posts in Markdown format, and then use Hugo static site generator to generate HTML files. The topic of this blog post is how those HTML files are served to you.
If you happened to come across my GopherCon 2021 lightning talk, this blog post describes the topic in all the gory detail!
Background Content delivery - Proof of Concept Content Delivery - Caddy as a reverse proxy Automating restart on updates Zero downtime updates Summary Background When you type in https://practicalgobook.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello world</title>
      <link>https://practicalgobook.net/posts/hello_world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://practicalgobook.net/posts/hello_world/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone. &amp;ldquo;Practical Go: Building Scalable Network and Non-Network Applications&amp;rdquo; is now out electronically as well as in print.
The book targets readers who have learned the Go language basics - syntax, understanding of types, being able to write functions (details are available in the &amp;ldquo;Getting started&amp;rdquo; chapter - but essentially, just a passing familiarity with the language is enough I think). I say that and reasonably confidently since that&amp;rsquo;s where I was when I started writing this book.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
