<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>articles on Practical Go - Book Website</title>
    <link>https://practicalgobook.net/categories/articles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in articles on Practical Go - Book Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://practicalgobook.net/categories/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Using SQLite from Go</title>
      <link>https://practicalgobook.net/posts/go-sqlite-no-cgo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://practicalgobook.net/posts/go-sqlite-no-cgo/</guid>
      <description>In the book, we used MySQL server as a way to store relational data from our applications. In this post, we will see how to use work with SQLite from Go.
The demo code used is available in this repository.
The table names and operations are intentionally chosen to losely match that of the official Go Project tutorial, Accessing a relational database which uses MySQL as the database server.
Let&amp;rsquo;s get started!</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Source Code and Errata Updates</title>
      <link>https://practicalgobook.net/posts/new_code_release_1_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://practicalgobook.net/posts/new_code_release_1_1/</guid>
      <description>I have published a new version of the source code accompanying the book.
You can find the v1.0.1 release here.
I am extremely thankful to the folks who reported and participated in the issues and pull requests.
The errata page has also been updated with a new error reported.
If you find a bug or missing source code, please file a GitHub issue or contact me at mail@practicalgobook.net.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The server powering practicalgobook.net</title>
      <link>https://practicalgobook.net/posts/blog_internals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://practicalgobook.net/posts/blog_internals/</guid>
      <description>I write my blog posts in Markdown format, and then use Hugo static site generator to generate HTML files. The topic of this blog post is how those HTML files are served to you.
If you happened to come across my GopherCon 2021 lightning talk, this blog post describes the topic in all the gory detail!
Background Content delivery - Proof of Concept Content Delivery - Caddy as a reverse proxy Automating restart on updates Zero downtime updates Summary Background When you type in https://practicalgobook.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello world</title>
      <link>https://practicalgobook.net/posts/hello_world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://practicalgobook.net/posts/hello_world/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone. &amp;ldquo;Practical Go: Building Scalable Network and Non-Network Applications&amp;rdquo; is now out electronically as well as in print.
The book targets readers who have learned the Go language basics - syntax, understanding of types, being able to write functions (details are available in the &amp;ldquo;Getting started&amp;rdquo; chapter - but essentially, just a passing familiarity with the language is enough I think). I say that and reasonably confidently since that&amp;rsquo;s where I was when I started writing this book.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
